The natural physics don't apply to me no more I
can't feel the boots resting on the cabin floor
The medical bay is quiet and the damage is done
I'm a stationary moon staring at a distant sun
I got the six strings resting heavy on my knee
Trying to remember how the engine used to be My
hands are still calloused, my grip is still
tight Just trying to find the gravity in the
middle of the night
The thrusters are cold, the lower decks are
dark, but I'm blowing on the embers of a heavy
metal spark. If the planet won't hold me, if the
orbit is dead, I'm gonna have to spin the metal
whole instead. Artificial gravity! Building
up the pressure inside of me Artificial gravity
A heavy rotation so the pilot can see If the
natural pull is permanently gone I'll engineer
the weight just to carry on Making my own
Artificial gravity
It's a stalemate here in the center of the void
Picking up the pieces of the ship that got
destroyed I'm mapping out the protocols,
tracking every hour Rerouting the cables to the
auxiliary power
Can't stand up to look out of the glass But I can
feel the friction of the cosmic dust pass
The thrusters are cold, the lower decks are
dark, but I'm blowing on the embers of a heavy
metal spark. If the planet won't hold me, if the
orbit is dead, I'm gonna have to spin the metal
whole instead. Artificial gravity! Building
up the pressure inside of me Artificial gravity
A heavy rotation so the pilot can't see If the
natural pull is permanently gone I'll engineer
the weight just to carry on Making my own
Artificial gravity
The engine is quiet, but it hasn't stopped. The
pressure is holding. The anchor is dropped. I'm
spinning the wheel. I'm finding the ground. I'm
pulling the weight from the inside out.
Artificial gravity Building up the pressure
inside of me Artificial gravity A heavy
rotation so the pilot can't see If the natural
pull is permanently gone I'll engineer the
weight just to carry on Making my own Artificial
gravity
I'll engineer the way The state will make it
Artificial gravity